<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Spaghetti Out The Window</title>
    <link href="https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io" />
    <updated>1969-12-31T19:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>MrFreshy</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Making websites was never my forte</title>
        <author>
            <name>MrFreshy</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/making-websites-was-never-my-forte-2.html"/>
        <id>https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/making-websites-was-never-my-forte-2.html</id>

        <updated>2020-07-29T14:29:04-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I have been involved with tech pretty deeply over multiple decades, and have at times wanted to have a place to post up my thoughts about random topics. For some reason, making websites has never made lot of sense to me. I have never wanted&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__image"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/coketurkey.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 48em) 100vw, 768px" srcset="https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-xs.jpg 300w ,https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-sm.jpg 480w ,https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-md.jpg 768w ,https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-lg.jpg 1024w ,https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-xl.jpg 1360w ,https://mrfreshy.github.io/mrfreshy.github.io/media/posts/3/responsive/coketurkey-2xl.jpg 1600w"  alt=""></figure>
<p>I have been involved with tech pretty deeply over multiple decades, and have at times wanted to have a place to post up my thoughts about random topics. For some reason, making websites has never made lot of sense to me. I have never wanted to take the time to learn how to code a site. </p>
<p>There have been multiple attempts at using this tool or that tool, but even this far into the timeline of websites being a thing, it still isn't EASY. WYSIWYG editing is supposed to make it simple to make what you look at as you design into a presentable website. Every attempt I have made over the years has ended up an exercise in frustration and an abandoned project.</p>
<p>Getting text posted up seems easy enough, but adding a photo can be maddening. I don't get it, and don't actually want to get it. There are not many topics that I actively just don't want to know, but this is one of them. </p>
<p>All of that being blah'd, here I am again with an attempt at making something happen. I am using a tool that seems to be okay, but we shall see once I attempt to add an image here and then publish.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
